<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Follett Destiny</string>

    <!--Fragment name-->
    <string name="CheckoutPatronListFragment">CheckoutPatronListFragment</string>

    <!-- Custom CustomAlert Text-->
    <string name="alert_wait">Loading. Please wait</string>
    <string name="alert_text">Alert Message!</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="net">Net</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="update">UPDATE</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="alert_warning">Information</string>
    <string name="alert_success">Alert</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="app_status_title">DESTINY</string>
    <string name="connect_your_school_label">Connect to Your School</string>
    <string name="select_district_label">Select District</string>
    <string name="select_school_label">Select School</string>
    <string name="get_started_label">Get Started</string>
    <string name="loading_label">Please wait...</string>
    <string name="no_internet_title">No Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="no_internet_des">Please try again when you have a better connection.</string>
    <string name="double_quote">\"</string>

    <!--Home screen-->
    <string name="home">HOME</string>
    <string name="checkInCheckout">" Check Out\nCheck In"</string>
    <string name="patronStatus">"Patron\nStatus"</string>
    <string name="itemStatus">Item Status</string>
    <string name="inventory">Inventory</string>
    <string name="receive">Receive</string>

    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>

    <!-- Checkin Checkout Screen-->
    <string name="checkin">Check In</string>
    <string name="checkout">Check Out</string>
    <string name="checkinChecoutTitle">Check Out/Check In</string>
    <string name="findPatron">Find Patron</string>
    <string name="enterBarcode">Enter Barcode</string>
    <string name="scan">SCAN</string>
    <string name="Go">GO</string>
    <string name="library">LIBRARY</string>
    <string name="resource">RESOURCE</string>
    <string name="titleDetails">Title Details</string>\
    <string name="additional_info_title">Additional Info</string>
    <string name="checkoutLabel">"Checked Out: "</string>
    <string name="overdueLabel">"Overdue: "</string>
    <string name="checkedin">Checked In</string>
    <string name="checkedOut">Checked Out</string>
    <string name="checkedOutBlocked">Checkout Blocked</string>
    <string name="allow">Allow</string>
    <string name="squareB">[%s]</string>
    <string name="recordInLibrary">Record In-Library Usage</string>


    <!--Patron Screen-->
    <string name="selectPatron">Select Patron</string>
    <string name="errorPatronEntry">You must enter a patron barcode or name.</string>
    <string name="barcodeLabel">Barcode: </string>
    <string name="homeRoomLabel">HomeRoom: </string>
    <string name="gradeLevelLabel">Grade Level: </string>


    <!--Login-->
    <string name="basic_label">BASIC</string>
    <string name="advanced_label">ADVANCED</string>
    <string name="library_label">Enter Destiny URL or IP Address</string>
    <string name="port_label">Port Number (e.g. 80)</string>
    <string name="ssl_port_label">SSL Port Number (e.g. 443)</string>
    <string name="connect_label">connect</string>
    <string name="url_empty_label">URL cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="port_empty_lable">Port cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="ssl_port_empty_lable">SSL port cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="username_empty_lebel">User ID cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="password_empty_lebel">Password cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_servername">Server name is invalid.</string>
    <string name="ssl_error">An SSL Error has occurred and the secure connection to the server cannot be made</string>
    <string name="error_sorry_school_not_setup">This app requires your school to have Destiny version 10.5 or higher installed.</string>
    <string name="error_unable_to_communicate">Unable to communicate with server.</string>
    <string name="error_load_prefs">Unable to load preferences.</string>
    <string name="school_noschoollist">No School Listed</string>
    <string name="no_district_list">No District Listed</string>
    <string name="dont_see_your_district">DON`T SEE YOUR DISTRICT?</string>
    <string name="dont_see_your_school">DON`T SEE YOUR SCHOOL?</string>
    <string name="additional_info">ADDITIONAL INFO</string>
    <string name="no_district">No district available</string>
    <string name="no_schools">No schools are configured in %s. Please contact your system administrator.</string>
    <string name="user_id">User ID</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">LOG IN</string>
    <string name="invalid_user_id">Invalid username or password.</string>
    <string name="log_in_to_a_different_server">LOG IN TO A DIFFERENT SERVER</string>

    <!-- Additional Info and More Details-->
    <string name="item_description">Description</string>
    <string name="item_availability">Availability</string>
    <string name="item_rating">Rating : </string>
    <string name="item_status">Status</string>
    <string name="item_titleby">Titles By</string>
    <string name="item_published">Published</string>
    <string name="item_edition">Edition</string>
    <string name="item_format">Format</string>
    <string name="item_isbn">ISBN</string>
    <string name="item_target">Target Audience </string>
    <string name="item_accelerated">AR</string>
    <string name="item_status_in">Status : IN</string>
    <string name="item_status_out">Status : Out</string>
    <string name="item_callno">Call# </string>
    <string name="itemstatus_callno">Call #: </string>
    <string name="of">\tof \t</string>
    <string name="item_quiz_no">Quiz Number: </string>
    <string name="item_points">, Points : </string>
    <string name="intent_titlemoredetails">titleMoreDetails</string>
    <string name="available_txt">\tAvailable</string>
    <string name="one">1</string>
    <string name="nullCheck">Null</string>

    <!--Item Status-->
    <string name="findItem">Find Item</string>
    <string name="item_status_title">Item Status</string>
    <string name="item_not_found">Copy %s not found</string>
    <string name="copyitem_not_found">Item %s not found</string>


    <!-- Intent data passing strings-->
    <string name="scanPatron">scanPatron</string>


    <!-- Log Error Message -->
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="scanPatronError">Scan patron error</string>
    <string name="noDataFound">no data found from api result</string>

    <!--Patron Status-->
    <string name="patron_status">Patron \nStatus</string>
    <string name="patron_status_label">Patron Status</string>
    <string name="patron_not_found">Patron %s not found</string>
    <string name="items_overude_label">items overdue</string>
    <string name="onhold_label">items on hold</string>
    <string name="title_hold_count">Hold (%s)</string>
    <string name="item_checkout_count">Check Outs (%s)</string>
    <string name="fines_count">Fines (%s)</string>
    <string name="barcodelabel">Barcode: %s</string>
    <string name="homeroomlabel">HomeRoom: %s</string>
    <string name="gradelevellabel">Grade Level: %s</string>
    <string name="barcode_label">Barcode: %s</string>
    <string name="due_label">Due: %s</string>
    <string name="item_checkout_label">Check Outs</string>
    <string name="library_title_label">Library Titles</string>
    <string name="resource_item_label">Resource Items</string>
    <string name="on_hold_label">Hold</string>
    <string name="fine_label">Fines</string>
    <string name="overdue_label">Overdue</string>

    <!-- Info Screen-->
    <string name="info">Follett Destiny Version %1$s</string>
    <string name="copyright_info">Copyright 2018 Follet School Solutions. \nA Follett Corporation Company. \nAll Rights Reserved. \n \nBuild %1$s \nAPI Version: %2$s</string>
    <string name="view_legel">VIEW LEGAL</string>
    <string name="site_info">Site: %1$s</string>
    <string name="user_info">User: %1$s</string>
    <string name="note">Note: If your library uses Standard Interleaved 2 of 5 or Standard Codabr barcodes, turn Follett decoding off. </string>
    <string name="rate_follett_destiny">RATE FOLLETT DESTINY</string>
    <string name="change_site">CHANGE SITE</string>
    <string name="logout">LOG OUT</string>

    <!--Inventory-->
    <string name="inventoryTitle">Inventory</string>
    <string name="viewSelection">VIEW SELECTIONS</string>
    <string name="selectInventory">Select Inventory</string>

    <!-- Inventory -->
    <string name="finalize_inventory">Finalize Inventory</string>
    <string name="unaccounted_copies">%1$d copies unaccounted</string>
    <string name="mark_lost">MARK LOST</string>
    <string name="ignore">IGNORE</string>
    <string name="call_numbers_text">To specify a call number range, enter at least the first 3 digits of each Dewy number or a complete call number prefix.</string>
    <string name="call_from">Call Numbers from:</string>
    <string name="call_num">Call Number</string>
    <string name="call_to">To:</string>
    <string name="enter_date">Enter Date</string>

    <string name="newInventory">NEW INVENTORY</string>
    <string name="newInventoryName">New Inventory Name</string>
    <string name="limitedToLabel">Limited to: </string>
    <string name="resourceTypesLabel">Resource Types</string>
    <string name="purchasePriceLabel">Purchase Price</string>
    <string name="includeItemsLabel">Include Items</string>
    <string name="checkoutHandlingLabel">Checkout Handling</string>
    <string name="excludeItems">Exclude Items Seen On or After</string>
    <string name="mismatchedItemLocationLabel">Mismatched Item Location</string>
    <string name="startInventory">Start Inventory</string>
    <string name="scanLocation">SCAN LOCATION</string>
    <string name="inventoryLocation">Inventory Location</string>
    <string name="circulationTypeLabel">Circulation Types</string>
    <string name="callNumbersLabel">Call Numbers:</string>




    <string name="legalTitle">Legal</string>
    <string name="legal_text">LIMITED USER LICENSE AGREEMENT\n
This license agreement (\"Agreement\") governs your use of Follett Software Company\'s (\"Follett\") library, media, asset and textbook management products listed on Follett\'s Web sites, including at www.follettsoftware.com, and any revisions and updates to such products including any software, data, reports and/or other instructional materials provided with the products or generated by the products (collectively \"Follett Technology\"). The Follett Technology is owned by Follett and/or its third party licensors.  Please see http://www.follettsoftware.com/destiny/licenseagreement/OpenSource.pdf for a complete list of the third party open source contributors to the Follett Technology and their license terms regarding use of their open source code in the Follett Technology. The Product is protected by U.S. and international copyright law. Follett and its licensors retain all title to and ownership of the Follett Technology, with the exception of this limited use license.  Additionally, your use of the Follett Technology is also governed by the terms and conditions of agreement between Follett and your school. In the event of any conflict between the two agreements, the agreement between Follett and your school shall apply. By installing, accessing or using all or any portion of the Follett Technology, you agree to be bound by the terms of these Agreements. If you do not agree to the terms of these Agreements, do not install, access or use the Follett Technology. Each time you access the Follett Technology you signify your acceptance and agreement, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree with each provision of this Agreement, or you are not authorized to agree to and accept this Agreement, or you do not have the legal authority to agree to and accept this Agreement, you may not use the Follett Technology.\n
\n
1. THE LICENSE\n
\n
1.1 You have a nonexclusive and nontransferable license for limited access to the Follett Technology.\n
\n
1.2 The use of the Follett Technology shall be for personal, non-commercial, educational, and research purposes. Follett reserves the right in its sole discretion to terminate your access to and usage of the Follett Technology in the event that you violate the terms of use hereunder and you fail to reasonably remedy the violation within 30 days of receiving such notice. You may not sell, transfer, publish, disclose, display or otherwise make available the Follett Technology beyond the limits of the license set out above. You shall use reasonable care to protect the copyrights and trade secrets of Follett. Violation of this provision shall be the basis for immediate termination of this Agreement. Termination of this Agreement shall be in addition to and not in lieu of any other legal or equitable remedies available to Follett.\n
1.3 Your school has provided you with a used id and user password enabling you to access the Follett technology. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your password and agree not to post your password on any Web site accessible to the public. You agree to assume responsibility for the results of any misuse of your password and to report any misuse of the password immediately to your school.\n
\n
\n
1.4 Follett will not be responsible for technological changes, acts of God and other events outside its control that make it impossible for you to access the Follett Technology.\n
\n
2. COPYRIGHT \n
The Product is protected by U.S. and international copyright law. Follett Software Company and its licensors retain all title to and ownership of the Follett Technology.\n
\n
3. THIRD PARTY WEB SITES\n
The Follett Technology may provide you with links to third party Web sites. You acknowledge that Follett does not endorse or maintain control over and will not be liable for the content, advertising or other materials contained on such third party sites. Your use of the content, goods or services on any third party site will be governed by the terms on that site, if any. You will be responsible for understanding and complying with third party sites\' terms of use and instructing your patrons and employees on the same.\n
4. CHILDREN\'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (\"COPPA\") \n
As required under COPPA, Follett must make the following disclaimer: FOLLETT SOFTWARE COMPANY DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION ABOUT CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13 THROUGH THE PRODUCT. Follett warrants that it will not use any information you provide for any purpose other than servicing your school\'s subscription, and that it will not disclose such information to any third party unless required by law. Follett cannot make that claim on behalf of third party sites found through the Follett technology. You therefore agree to inform and educate users under the age of 13 that they should not provide any personally identifying information on any third party sites without the involvement and verifiable consent of their parents.\n
\n
5. THIRD PARTY SERVICES\n
We allow third-party companies, including AddThis and Google, to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org\n
\n
5.  WARRANTY \n
Follett represents and warrants that it owns or controls all rights necessary and, has the authority to grant you access to the Follett Technology.  In addition, Follett represents and warrants that it has obtained all rights necessary in and to the Follett Technology.  This limited warranty does not cover any material defect or infringement resulting from any accident, abuse, or misapplication of the Follett Technology caused by you, or any modification you, make to the Follett Technology, whether or not such modification is authorized by Follett.\n
\n
6. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY.\n
FOLLETT DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.  FOLLETT IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THIRD PARTY NETWORK OPERATING SYSTEMS, COMPUTER HARDWARE, SOFTWARE OR PERIPHERALS THAT YOU USE IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE FOLLETT TECHNOLOGY, OR THAT ANY NETWORK-ACCESSIBLE FEATURES OF THE FOLLETT TECHNOLOGY WILL BE CONTINUALLY ACCESSIBLE OR ACCESSIBLE AT ANY TIME.   THE THIRD PARTY SOURCE CODE USED IN THE PRODUCT AND ITS LICENSING TERMS ARE AVAILABLE AT http://www.follettsoftware.com/destiny/licenseagreement/OpenSource.pdf, AND IS PROVIDED BY THIRD PARTY LICENSORS \"AS IS,\" WHO DISCLAIM ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE CONTENT IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” BASIS AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED AND NEITHER FOLLETT NOR ITS CONTENT PROVIDERS MAKE ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY (WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED) ABOUT THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE CONTENT.\n
\n
7. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n
 IN PROVIDING THE FOLLETT TECHNOLOGY, NEITHER FOLLETT NOR ANY OF THE CONTENT PROVIDERS, NOR ANY OF THIRD PARTY LICENSORS OR THEIR CONTRIBUTORS WILL BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOST PROFITS OR BUSINESS OPPORTUNITIES, LOSS OF USE, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF DATA, OR ANY OTHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, PRODUCT LIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. THIS LIMITATION SHALL APPLY REGARDLESS OF WHETHER FOLLETT HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. FOLLETT\'S LIABILITY UNDER THIS EULA WILL NOT, IN ANY EVENT, EXCEED THE FEES, IF ANY, PAID BY YOU TO FOLLETT FOR ACCESSING FOLLETT TECHNOLOGY LICENSED BY YOU UNDER THIS EULA.\n
\n
8.  GOVERNING LAW\n
This agreement shall be interpreted and construed according to, and governed by, the laws of the State of Illinois, United States of America.\n
</string>

</resources>
